http://kapeinsurance.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyHomepage > Privacy PolicyWe value your privacy! We will never give, lease, sell or otherwise disclose your personal information. Period! Any information you give to Kape Insurance Agency at any of our sites (including: www.kapeinsurance.com) will be held with the utmost care, and will not be used in ways to which you have not consented. A more detailed explanation about how we safeguard your personal information is described below. If you have any questions at all about our privacy policy, please call us.RESALE OR DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIESKape Insurance Agency does not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease any personal information collected at our site, including contact forms, download requests or email lists.BROWSER INFORMATION COLLECTED ON THE WEB SITEKape Insurance Agency analyzes the website analytics to improve the value of the materials available on the web site. Contact UsFull Name:*Email:* Phone:Insurance Interest:-- Choose One --Business InsurancePersonal InsuranceComments:CAPTCHAEmailThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
It Might Be Time to Think About Spring Cleaning Your InsuranceSpring may be the time of year for cleaning out closets and drawers and organizing attics and cellars, but it also is a great time to clean up your insurance coverages. It is important to look at your insurance coverage at least once a year. As your life changes so do your insurance needs. Call […]Read More Website Theme by Web Themes Plus | A ThinkSEM Company
